The Dancing Dump Truck
Hey, cool moves!
Huh? Who the heck is that?
No one invited you, weirdo.
Come on, be a good sport and let me in on the fun!
Woohoo! Hahaha!
Huh? Hey! No fair, guys!
Ugh...
Save me, brave warrior!
Wahaha! It's no use crying now!
The world belongs to Vance, the Demon King!
Not so fast, Demon King Vance!
Is that Jun, the warrior?
What? How did he make his way through all of our troops?!
Looks like I'll have to teach him a lesson myself!
Take them on, Blue Cop!
Aaugh!
Mr. Warrior!
I have come to save you, Princess Anna!
Thank you very much, Jun!
Ahh... Princess Anna... one little kiss on this cheek too, please...
Wake up!
Hey, mom... good morning...
Don't you "good morning" me!
You promised to help out at the restaurant today, remember?
Right, I just remembered...
Jun, here's a cheeseburger.
Yes, Dad.
Table number two.
I got it, Dad.
One cheeseburger, coming up!
The coffee here is the best in town. No joke.
Saying that won't get you a free refill, officer.
Welcome!
Jun, I think they're here for you.
For me?
Come on in.
Good day, ma'am!
Vance and Lavi?
What are you guys doing here?
What do you mean? This is a restaurant, we're obviously here to eat!
That's not it!
Sit down. We wanna talk.
Huh? But I'm...
Uh... Welcome, we have a corner table for two, right this way.
What did you want to talk about?
It's about the robot that attacked you.
Uh... robot?
Don't play dumb!
We know what we saw. On that bridge over the underpass...
Well, it's...
Jun. Please keep this a secret between us.
Secret?
If the people of Earth find out about the Metal Cardbots, they will get frightened. I don't want to cause any trouble.
Don't worry, It's a promise!
Uhhh...
We're going to be in middle school next year! "Ah! Robots!!"
If we went around acting like that, Anna would surely laugh at us.
That's just like Vance was saying the other day!
Cram it, will ya? I'm leaving!
B-But, Vance! Don't you want to eat first?!
Have a nice day.
Hey, don't you want a smoothie before you go?
Yeah! Can I get a-
Hurry up!
Ah, maybe next time... wait up, Vance!
What'd they stop by for?
Beats me.
A giant robot was spotted in a carpark under an overpass last night.
A giant robot?
Here is the black box recording that became a hot topic over the Internet.
According to an eyewitness, a dump truck approached when he and his friends were dancing...
-That's...
-transformed into a humanoid robot, and started dancing along.
-Wow, that video looks so real. You can do a lot with CGI these days.
- The viewers are divided over whether this video is real or fake...
Yeah... it looks like a movie, haha...
I heard the new Max Force movie is coming out soon. Whaddya say I take you to go see it?
Ah! Dear!
Yes- Oh, oh no!
That's coming out of your paycheck!
Oh no, not again!
There's no mistaking it. That's Mega Trucker.
Is that right?
I told him over and over again to lay low and not attract the attention of the natives.
What are you going to do? This already has over a million views, it's gone viral!
He won't listen to me anyway.
We'll just have to seal him.
Seal him?
With the power of the Metal Breath, you can seal a Metal Cardbot inside a Metal Card.
In any case, I need to try to convince Mega Trucker once more.
Yeah, but to do that, we have to go find him first...
Jun. Do you think you could procure a large speaker?
A speaker?
I think I have an idea.
It's hard waking up so early. This will be over before school, right?
For this plan to work, we'll have to do it while it's quiet out, and when no one's watching.
If you're tired, I can make you some coffee when this is done.
I'm too young to drink coffee- wait, you know how to make coffee?
Mega Trucker loves music. His favorite is Musica Latina.
He can't help but dance anytime he hears it.
How about that?
That's perfect.
Let's turn up the volume.
Alright.
Don't you think this is too loud?
It's not loud enough.
Woohoo! This is just my kind of music! Beep Beep!
He actually showed up?!
Let me in on the fun!
Hehehe!
This is great! Step on the gas and let's dance the night away!
Mega Trucker! I told you to lay low and not be seen by anyone!
Why won't you listen?!
You can be boring if you want! I'll live my life dancing and having fun!
Jun, get back!
Hey! Bring the music back!
I can't let you destroy Uncle Edo's repair shop!
Who's this kid, anyway?
We have lost our home and have no choice but to live here on this planet!
We must learn to get along with the people of Earth, like this boy!
Shut up! Don't you tell me what to do ever again!
Blue Cop!
Blue Cop! Are you alright?
I guess we have no choice. We'll have to seal him.
Jun! The time has come for us to fight.
So it's come to this. Stay calm... what should I do?
Mega Power Tackle!
Alright- Huh? Look out, Blue Cop!
Now, Jun!
Blue Cop, setup!
Huh? So you do know how to fight!
Uhh... T-Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt Smaaaa-
Uhh..heheh... sorry...
Hahaha! How pathetic!
After all that talk, you can't even throw a punch?
Blue Cop!
Jun, I'm okay! Just give me the next command!
Blue Cop, Burst Shot!
Burst Shot!
Great!
Burst Shot, Burst Shot, Burst Shot!
This is the end!
Megabolt Punch!
Megabolt...
Punch!!
Jun, seal him now!
N-Now? Alright...
Metal Cardbot... Change Up!
Mega Trucker... sealed!
Well done, Jun. You did it.
Mega Trucker really turned into a card...
Correct. He has become a Metal Card and can now be stored within the Metal Breath.
You can summon Mega Trucker any time you want with that card,
and you can give him commands too.
What's going on? What was that just now?
Uhh...
Uh, Uncle Edo...
This is bad...